Finding Aid for the Charles S. Mitchell Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Playbills and Programs
  - Children's Hour by Lillian Hellman - Maxine Elliott's Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Dead End by Sidney Kingsley - Belasco Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Idiot's Delight by Robert Sherwood - Sam. S. Shubert Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Victoria Regina by Laurence Housman - Broadhurst Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Federal Theatre Presents Summer 1938 Program (Box 3)
  - Blithe Spirit by Noel Coward - Booth Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Eve of St. Mark by Maxwell Anderson - Cort Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Gondoliers by W. S. Gilbert and Arthur Sullivan - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Hello Out There by William Saroyan Magic by G. K. Chesterton - Belasco Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Janie by Antoinette Perry - Henry Miller's Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Petticoat Forever by Mark Reed - Nashville Community Theatre (Box 3)
  - Sons O' Fun by Ole Olsen and Chic Johnson - Winter Garden Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Strip for Action by Howard Lindsay and Russell Crouse - National Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Uncle Harry by Thomas Job - Hudson Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Claudia by Rose Franken - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The Doughgirls by Joseph Fields - Lyceum Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Harriet by Florence Ryerson and Colin Clements - Henry Miller's Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Kiss and Tell by F. Hugh Herbert - Biltmore Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Merry Widow - Majestic Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Lady in the Dark by Moss Hart - Civic Opera House, Chicago (Box 3)
  - The Philadelphia Story by Philip Barry - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Porgy and Bess by George Gershwin and Du Bose Heyard - Forty-fourth Street Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Tomorrow the World by James Gow and Arnaud d'Usseau - Ethel Barrymore Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace by Joseph Kesselring - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Buddies by George V. Hobart - Produced by Smyrna Army and Field Dramatic Club - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Chicken Every Sunday by Julius J. and Philip G. Epstein - Plymouth Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Decision by Edward Chodorov - Ambassador Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Jacobonsky and the Colonel (original play) by Franz Werfel (American play) by S. N. Behrman - Martin Beck Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Letters to Lucerne by Fritz Rotter and Allen Vincent - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The New Moon: An Operetta in Three Acts by Sigmund Romberg, Oscar Hammerstein 2nd, Frank Mandel, and Laurence Schwab - New York City Center of Music and Drama (Box 3)
  - Othello by William Shakespeare starring Paul Robeson - Sam S. Shubert Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Searching Wind by Lillian Hellman - Fulton Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Spring Again by Isabel Leighton and Bertram Bloch - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - 3 Is a Family by Phoebe and Henry Ephron - Belasco, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Voice of the Turtle by John Van Druten - Moresco Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - A Bell for Adano by Paul Osborn (based on John Hersey's novel) - Cort Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Barretts of Wimpole Street by Rudolf Besier - Ethel Barrymore Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Dark of the Moon by Howard Richardson and William Berney - Forty-Sixth Street Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Dinner at Eight by Edna Ferber and George S. Kaufman - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Foolish Notion by Philip Barry (starring Tallulah Bankhead) - Martin Beck Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Foxhole in the Parlor by Elsa Shelley - The Booth Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Harvey by Mary Chase - Forty-Eighth Street Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Hasty Heart by John Patrick - Hudson Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - *Second Decade of the Playhouse, a Publication of the Nashville Community Playhouse, Oct. 8, 1945 - Nashville (Box 3)
  - Hollywood Pinafore (Or the Lad Who Loved a Salary) (book and lyrics revised by George S. Kaufman - Alvin Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - I Remeber Mama by John Van Druten (music by Richard Rogers and Oscar Hammerstein, 2nd) - The Music Box, New York City (Box 3)
  - Oklahoma! (based on the play "Green Grow the Lilacs" by Lynn Riggs) (music by Richard Rogers and Oscar Hammerstein, 2nd) - St. James Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Old Ladies by Rodney Ackland (adapted from a novel by Hugh Walpole) - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Little Women (The Theatre Guild on the Air: American Broadcasting Company) (starring Katharine Hepburn) (Box 3)
  - My Sister Eileen by Joseph Fields and Jerome Chodoroc - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Nashville Community Playhouse Membership 1945-46 (Box 3)
  - Private Lives by Noel Coward - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Song of Norwey (a new Operetta on the life and music of Edvard Grieg) (musical adaptation and lyrics) by Robert Wright and George Forrest and (book) by Milton Lazarus (from a play by Homer Curran) Choreography by George Balanchine - The Imperial Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth by Thornton Wilder - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The Time of Your Life by William Saroyan - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Uncle Harry by Thomas Job - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Angel Street by Patrick Hamilton - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Carousel (a new musical play based on Ferenc Molnar's "Liliom" as adapted by Benjamin F. Glazier) by Richard Rogers and Oscar Hammerstein - Majestic Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Deep Are the Roots by Arnaud d'Usseau and James Gow (staged by Elia Kazan) - Fulton Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Gypsy Lady (a period piece created to re-introduce music by Victor Herbert)(combines melodies of 2 of his most distinguished operettas, "The Fortune Teller" and "The Serenade") (Musical adaptation and Choral arrangements by Arthur Kay) (book by Henry Myers) and (new lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest) - Century Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Hamlet by William Shakespeare - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Hosea: A Cantata by F. Arthur Henkel, given Sunday, October 6, 1946--8 p.m. at Christ's Church, Nashville, Tennessee (Box 3)
  - Jooss Ballett, Artistic Director Kurt Jooss, Performed Thursday, November 7, 1946--8:15 p.m. - Ryman Auditorium, Nashville (Box 3)
  - Nashville Community Playhouse Announcement of Twelfth Season: 1946-47 (Box 3)
  - Old Vic Theatre Company (Henry IV, Part 1; Henry IV, Part 2; Uncle Vanya; Oedipus, English version by W. B. Yeats; The Critic by William Sheridan), presented May 6 to June 15 (First American Engagement of Old Vic) - New Century Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - State of the Union by Howard Lindsay and Russel Crouse - Hudson Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Swan Song by Ben Hecht and Charles MacArthur - Booth Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Tonight at Eight-Thirty by Noel Coward - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - All My Sons by Arthur Miller (staged by Elia Kazan) - Coronet Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Born Yesterday by Garson Kanin - Lyceum Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Brigadoon (book and lyrics) by Alan Jay Lerner and (music) by Frederick Loewe - Ziegfeld Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Call Me Mister (music and lyrics) by Harold Rome - Blackstone Theatre, Chicago (Box 3)
  - Command Decision by William Wister Haines - Fulton Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - Cradle Snatchers by Russell G. Medcraft and Norma Mitchell - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Duet for Two Hands by Mary Hayley Bell - Booth Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Glass Menagerie by Tennessee Williams - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The Happiest Days of Your Life by John Dighton - Apollo Theatre London, England (Box 3)
  - Happy Birthday (2) by Anita Loos (starring Helen Hayes) Rogers and Hammerstein Production - Broadhurst Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Heiress by Ruth and Augustus Goetz (starring Basil Rathbone) - Biltmore Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - How I Wonder by Donald Ogden Stewart - Hudson Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - The Iceman Cometh by Eugene O'Neill - Studebaker Theatre, Chicago (Box 3)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest by Oscar Wilde - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Joan of Lorraine by Maxwell Anderson - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Program for Tuesday, October 28, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Of Thee I Sing (music) by George Gershwin and (lyrics) by Ira Gershwin - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Rain by John Colton and Clemence Randolph - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The Taming of the Shrew by William Shakespeare - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - The Tempest by William Shakespeare - Nashville Community Playhouse (Box 3)
  - Under the Counter by Arthur Macrae (music) by Manning Sherwin and (lyrics) by Harold Purcell - Sam. S. Shubert Theatre, New York City (Box 3)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire by Tennessee Williams (Elia Kazan production) - Ethel Barrymore Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Charley's Aunt by Brandon Thomas - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Edward, My Son by Robert Morly and Noel Langley - Martin Beck Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Inside U.S.A. (lyrics and music) by Howard Dietz and Arthur Schwartz - Majestic Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Magdalena by Heitor Villa-Lobos (pattern and lyrics) by Robert Wright and George Forrest (book) by Frederick Hazlitt Brennan and Homer Curran - Ziegfeld Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Mister Roberts by Thomas Heggen and Joshua Logan - Alvin Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Program for Tuesday, March 29, 1948 - Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Shanghai Gesture by John Colton - Nashville Community Playhouse N (Box 4)
  - Radio City Music Hall Program for week beginning Thursday, Oct. 7, 1948 - New York City (Box 4)
  - The Respectful Prostitute by Jean-Paul Sartre (adapted from French by Eva Walas) together with Hope is the Thing with Feathers by Richard Harrity - Cort Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Summer and Smoke by Tennessee Williams - Music Box New York City (Box 4)
  - The Voice of the Turtle by John Van Druten - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Anne of the Thousand Days by Maxwell Anderson - Schubert Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Happy Birthday by Anita Loos - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Les Sylphides (ballet music) by Frederic Chopin - Sadler's Wells Ballet London (Box 4)
  - Macbeth by William Shakespeare - Shakespeare Memorial Theatre Stratfox -upon- Avon (Box 4)
  - The Madwoman of Chaillot by Jean Giraudoux - Belasco Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream by William Shakespeare - Shakespeare Memorial Theatre Stratfox -upon- Avon (Box 4)
  - Roberta by Alice Duer Miller - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Spider by Fulton Oursler and Lowell Brentano - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Heiress by Ruth and Augustus Goetz - Theatre Royal London (Box 4)
  - Program for Old Vic Theatre Company, 1948-1949 Season - New Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Ridgeway's Late Joys by Peter Ridgeway and Leonard Sachs - Villiers Street London (Box 4)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire by Tennessee Williams - Ethel Barrymore Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - That Lady by Kate O'Brien - Martin Beck Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Menu from Lucerne, Switzerland (Box 4)
  - Shakespeare Memorial Theatre Programme, April 16-June 11 (Box 4)
  - Edinburgh International Festival of Music and Drama Program, August 21-September 11 (Box 4)
  - Born Yesterday by Garson Kanin - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Henry IV by Shakespeare - Sewanee, Tennessee (Box 4)
  - The Madwoman of Chaillot by Jean Giraudoux - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Romeo and Juliet by Shakespeare - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Royal Family by George S. Kaufman and Edna Ferber - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Program for April 3 - Ryman Auditorium Nashville (Box 4)
  - Finian's Rainbow (book) by E. Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy, (lyrics) by E. Y. Harburg, (Music) by Burton Lane - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Season in the Sun by Wolcott Gibbs - Cort Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Program for April 3 - Ryman Auditorium Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Players Bulletin, Spring 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Red Mill by Victor Herbert and Henry Blossom - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Dark is Light Enough by Christopher Fry - Aldwych Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Les Sylphides, The Firebird, and La Boutique Fantasque - Sadler's Wells Ballet London (Box 4)
  - The Boy Friend by Sandy Wilson - Wyndam's Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Victoria Regina 100th Production of Nashville Community Playhouse - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Bad Seed by Maxwell Anderson - Aldwych Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Shadow of Doubt by Norman King (2 copies) - Saville Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Fings Ain't Wot They Used T'Be by Frank Norman and Lionel Bart - Garrick Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Merchant of Venice by Shakespeare - Old Vic Company Bristol (Box 4)
  - Romeo and Juliet by Shakespeare - Old Vic Company Bristol (Box 4)
  - Twelfth Night by Shakespeare - Old Vic Company Bristol (Box 4)
  - Orpheus in the Underworld by Jacques Offenbach and Hector Cremieux - Sadler's Wells Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Bishop's Bonfire by Sean O'Casey - Mermaid Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Five Plus One by Steven Vinaver and Carl Davis - Royal Lyceum Theatre Edinburgh (Box 4)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia by Gioacchino Rossini - King's Theatre Edinburgh (Box 4)
  - King John by Shakespeare - Assembly Hall Edinburgh (Box 4)
  - Let Wives Tak Tent by Robert Kemp - Gateway Theatre Edinburgh (Box 4)
  - ‘Tis Pity She's a Whore by John Ford - Mermaid Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Tragical History of Dr. Faustus by Christopher Marlowe - Assembly Hall Edinburgh (Box 4)
  - Wildest Dreams by Dorothy Reynolds and Julian Slade - Vaudeville Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Four Programs for the Edinburgh International Festival (Box 4)
  - Program for the Mermaid Theatre, June-September (Box 4)
  - "An Evening with Juliette Greco" - Royal Lyceum Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Camelot by Alan Jay Lerner and Frederick Loewe - War Memorial Opera House San Francisco (Box 4)
  - The Stephen Foster Story by Paul Green - My Old Kentucky Home Bardstown, K (Box 4)
  - Playbill for Auntie Mame, June 9, 1958 - Broadhurst Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Aladdin and his Wonderful Lamp - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Alice in Wonderland - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Candida by George Bernard Shaw - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - On Approval by Frederick Lonsdale - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Racket by Bartlett Cormack - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Wild Duck by Henrick Ibsen - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Charley's Aunt by Brandon Thomas - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Hay Fever by Noel Coward - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Liliom by Franz Molnar - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Sun-Up by Lula Vollmer - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Vortex by Noel Coward - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Children of the Moon by Martin Flavin - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Craig's Wife by George Kelly - Little Theatre Guild Bellamy Players Nashville (Box 4)
  - The Dover Road by A. A. Milne - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Erstwhile Susan by Marian De Forest - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Loose Ankles by Sam Janney - Little Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Recital by Helen Jepson - Metropolitan Opera Association Nashville (Box 4)
  - Anthonv and Cleopatra by Shakespeare starring Katherine Cornell (Box 4)
  - Petticoat Influence by Neil Grant starring Helen Hayes - Lyceum Theatre (Box 4)
  - Tomorrow and Tomorrow by Philip Barry - Henry Miller's Theatre New York City (Box 4)
  - Tristan et Isolde by Richard Wagner - Theatre Nat. de l'Opera Paris (Box 4)
  - Dark of the Moon: A Legend with Music by Howard Richardson and William Berney - New York City (Box 4)
  - Sketchbook on Cornelia Otis Skinner (Box 4)
  - Children of Earth by Alice Brown - Birm'gham (Box 4)
  - Daphne Laureola by James Birdie - Wyndham's Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The School for Scandal by Richard Brinsley Sheridan - Old Vic Theatre Company, New Theatre London (Box 4)
  - September Tide by Daphne du Maurier - Aldwych Theatre (Box 4)
  - Together Again by Jack Hylton - Victoria Palace London (Box 4)
  - Wappin' Wharf: A Frightful Comedy of Pirates by Charles S. Brooks - Jefferson Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Sketch book on Eva Le Gallienne (Box 4)
  - Two musical performances by "The Saltire Group" (Box 4)
  - Scotland in the Robin's Flight performed by Elizabeth Seton (Box 4)
  - A La Carte by Alan Melville and Charles Zwar - Savoy Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Abie's Irish Rose by Anne Nichols - Castle Square Theatre Boston (Box 4)
  - Anna Lucasta by Philip Yordan - His Majesty's Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Calumet Players' Presentation, The Gold Tooth by Andrew Lytle Greatness by Hale Sahneberger The Harvesters by Richard West Shadows by Tom Griscom (Box 4)
  - Casino de Paris (Box 4)
  - Little Lambs Eat Ivy by Noel Langley - Ambassadors Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Paragon by Roland and Michael Pertwee - Fortune Theatre London (Box 4)
  - The Rivals by Richard Brinsley Sheridan - Orpheum Theatre Nashville (Box 4)
  - Spider's Web by Agatha Christie - Savoy Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Traveller's Joy by Arthur MacRae - Criterion Theatre London (Box 4)
  - Watch on the Rhine by Lillian Hellman - Ryman Auditorium Nashville (Box 4)
  - You and I by Philip Barry - Little Theatre Birm'gham (Box 4)
  - Swan Song by Ben Hecht and Charles MacArthur - Nashville Community Playhouse Nashville (Box 4)
  - Three Scenes from Three Operas starring Salvatore Baccaloni (Box 4)
- Programs - Theatre Vendome Nashville, circa 1913-1916 (Box 5)
- Newspaper clippings on theatre (Box 5)
- Newspaper clippings of New York Times Shakespeare Tercentenary editions and a special edition of Stratford-upon-Avon Herald. (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets on theatre organizations and their histories (Box 5)
- History of Nashville, A. L. Crabb reports (Box 5)
- [Mitchell's] notes on theatre (Box 5)
- undated Francis Robinson press release (Box 5)
- Libettos (Box 5)
  Rigoletto by Verdi (published by Oliver Ditson)
  L'Oracolo by Camillo Zanoni (Scotti Grand Opera Co., published by Fred Rullman)
  The Jewels of the Madonna by Ermanno Wolf-Ferrari (published by G. Schirmer)
  Rigoletto by Verdi (published by Charles E. Burden)
  La Traviata by Verdi (published by Oliver Ditson)
  La Boheme by Puccini (Boston Grand Opera Season 1915-16, published by Charles E. Burden)
- Playbills given by Herschel Gower (Box 5)
  - Macbeth by Shakespeare - Edinburgh Int. Festival Church of Scotland Assembly Hall Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Poets in Public - Edinburgh Int. Festival Freemason's Hall Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - There Was a Man: A New Play about Robert Burns by Tom Wright - Morton House Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Fringe, a revue by Alan Bennett, Peter Cook, Jonathan Miller, Dudley Moore - May Fair Theatre London (Box 5)
  - Four Thousand Brass Halfpennies, adapted' from Dryden's "Amphittyon" by Bernard Miles - Mermaid Theatre London (Box 5)
  - Half a Sixpence by Beverly Cross and David Heneker - Broadhurst Theatre New York City (Box 5)
  - Portrait of a Queen by William Francis - Vaudeville Theatre London (Box 5)
  - Emlyn Williams as Charles Dickens - Globe Theatre London (Box 5)
  - Two Programs in German: "Porgy and Bess" by Gershwin and ‘ dame Butterfly" by Puccini (Box 5)
  - London Theatre Guide, September 6-September 11, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Musical Concert by Marlene Dietrich - Edinburgh Int. Festival Royal Lyceum Theatre Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - A Program of various plays (Program printed in Greek, English, French and German) - Epidaurus Theatre Greece (Box 5)
  - An Edinburgh Fancy by the Royal Scottish Country Dance Society - Royal High School Hall Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Edinburgh Int. Festival Program - Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Festival Fringe Society Program - Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - A Festival in the Royal Mile by the Saltire Society - Gladstone's Land Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Inaugural Service of Thanksgiving and Dedication for the Edinburgh Int. Festival - St. Giles' Cathedral Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Johnny So Long by Vivienne C. Welburn - Traverse Theatre Club Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Lysistrata by Aristophanes - Edinburgh University Theatre Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Music of Georgian Edinburgh by the Saltire Society - Gladstone's Land Edinburgh (Box 5)
  - Souvenir Programme, Edinburgh International Festival (Box 5)
  - The Burn by Kerry Lee - Oxford Theatre Group (Box 5)
- Photographs, many of which are unidentified, of theatrical performers (Box 6)